&gt;&gt; By the late aughts,
&gt;&gt; 2005年から2010年までに
the Internet had made it easier to generate and collect images,
インターネットは画像の生成と収拾を容易にし
storage costs had dropped so that it was cheap to save large collections of images,
ストレージコストが低下したため 大量の画像コレクションの保存が安くなり
and services like Amazon's Mechanical Turk had
AmazonのMechanical Turkなどのサービスによって
even made it more cost-effective to label images.
画像のラベル付けがさらに費用効果的になりました
That confluence of factors gave rise to ImageNet,
これらの要因の積み重ねによりImageNetが登場しました
a huge database of hand-labeled images.
これはハンドラベル画像の巨大なデータベースです
And the ImageNet database gave rise to
そしてImageNetデータベースから生まれたのが
the ImageNet Large Scale Visual Recognition Competition.
ImageNet Large Scale Visual Recognition Competitionです
&gt;&gt; The ImageNet Large Scale Visual Recognition Competition
&gt;&gt; ImageNet Large Scale Visual Recognition Competitionは
is most famous as an annual competition,
有名な年次大会であり
where teams from industry and academia try to build
企業や大学のチームがオブジェクト検出およびローカライゼーションのための
the best networks for object detection and localization.
ベストなネットワークの構築に取り組みます
&gt;&gt; Kind of like this image.
&gt;&gt; この画像を見てください
Is this a dog or a horse?
これは犬ですか 馬ですか
&gt;&gt; It's a horse.
&gt;&gt; 馬です
Anyway, this spurred really intense competition between teams in
とにかく この激烈なコンテストでは企業や大学のチームが
industry and academia to produce the best image classification network.
最良の画像分類ネットワークの作成に取り組みます
And as these teams published their approaches,
各チームはアプローチを公表するので
we learned a lot about the best ways to build neural networks.
ニューラルネットワーク構築の最良の方法について多くを学ぶことができます
The first big breakthrough was in 2012,
最初の大きなブレークスルーは2012年のことであり
when the winning submission really changed the field.
優勝チームはこの分野を変革しました
It was called AlexNet,
それはAlexNetという名前であり
and it looked a lot like Yann LeCun's neural network from way back in 1998.
1998年にさかのぼるYann LeCunのニューラルネットワークによく似ていました